ILGWU Audio-Visual (AV) 5780 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Man speaking sequence, money donations, retired strikers, contribution letters, rally (Box 39.5, Folder 10)
- Dubinsky, dues books, housing, Unity House, old Justice, old logos, immigrants, proclamation (Box 39.5, Folder 11)
- Strikers, workers, strike flyers (Box 39.5, Folder 12)
- Friendly visiting, club snapshots, club documents (Box 39.5, Folder 13)
- Politics, university, children workers, tenements, health center, old meetings, injuries (Box 39.5, Folder 14)
- Current members (Box 39.5, Folder 15)
- Old meetings, old slogans, money in hand (Box 39.5, Folder 16)
- [unlabelled loose slides, outs, duplicates], 1950 (Box 39.5, Folder 17)
  Slides; Includes program, music and lyrics by Michael Johnson, presented by the Northeast Department to the May 1950 ILGWU Convention
- E.C.T. Installation (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Cloak Joint Board Installation (Box 40, Folder 2a)
- Cloak Joint Board Installation (Box 40, Folder 2b)
- Local 10 Installation (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Opening Ceremonies, Training Institute (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Dress Joint Board Installation (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Keynote Address, 1950 Convention (Box 40, Folder 6a)
- Keynote Addres, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 6b)
- Keynote Address, 1950 Convention (Box 40, Folder 6c)
- Keynote Address, 1950 Convention (Box 40, Folder 6d)
- Lecture Training Institute (Box 40, Folder 7)
  (2 sides)
- Trade Union Comm., Liberal Party (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Local 38 Retirment Ceremonies (re-recording) (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Forward Hour, WEVD, Yiddish Political Talk (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Local 22 Election, Rally (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Yiddish Political Speech, WEVD (Box 40, Folder 12)
- ICTFu (International Confederation of Free Trade Unions) (Box 40, Folder 13a)
- ICTFU (International Confederation of Free Trade Unions) (Box 40, Folder 13b)
- ICTFU (International Confederation of Free Trade Unions) (Box 40a, Folder 13c)
- Dedication, Los Angeles Health Center; Ross-Levy-DD Dinner; H. Langer-DD (Box 40a, Folder 14a)
  2 sides
- Lecture Training Institute (Box 40a, Folder 15a)
- Lecture Training Institute (Box 40a, Folder 15b)
- Lecture to new class, Training Institute (Box 40a, Folder 17)
- Lecture to new class, Training Institute (Box 40a, Folder 18)
  part 2
- Graduation of First Class Training Institute (Box 40a, Folder 19)
- Northeast Conference Dinner Speech, Springfield, Massachusetts (Box 40a, Folder 20)
- Presentation to William Green, J.L.C. Ceremony (Box 40a, Folder 21)
- Yiddish Political Speech, WEVD-WLIB (Box 40a, Folder 22)
- NBC 20th Century Fund Program (Box 40a, Folder 23)
- Lecture to Training Institute (Box 40a, Folder 24)
- Lecture to Training Institute (Box 40a, Folder 25)
- Local 10 50th Anniversary celebration, Moe Falikman and George Meany (Box 40a, Folder 30a)
- Local 10 50th Anniversary celebration, David Dubinsky (Box 40a, Folder 30b)
- Garment Center Rally for Governor Stevensontaken from radio broadcast; David DubinskyGovernor Stevenson (Box 40a, Folder 31)
- Local 22 Installation, Manhattan Center, 1953 (Box 40a, Folder 32)
  May 4
- Local 117 Installation, Manhattan Center, 1953 (Box 40a, Folder 33a)
  March 11
- Local 117 Installation, Manhattan Center (continued), 1953 (Box 41, Folder 33b)
- Local 35 Installation, Hotel New Yorker (Box 41, Folder 34a)
- Local 35 Installation, Hotel New Yorker (Box 41, Folder 34b)
- Local #10 Installation, Manhattan Center (Box 41, Folder 35)
- Eastern Out-of-Town Installation, Hotel Astor, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  April 11
- David Dubinsky lecture to class at Training Institute, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 37a)
  May 6
- David Dubinsky lecture to Training Institute, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 37b)
- David Dubinsky lecture to Training Institute (about five minutes), 1953 (Box 41, Folder 37c)
- Training Institute, Graduation, Hochman, Dubinsky, Elder (2 sides), 1953 (Box 41, Folder 38a)
  May 28
- Training Institute, Graduation, Hochman, Stulberg, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 38b)
- Chicago Civic Opera House, Opening Session, ILGWU 28th convention, WCFL Broadcast, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  May 18
- ILGWU Council Room, Northeast Department Meeting (re: 35-hour week), David Gingold-David Dubinsky (Box 41, Folder 40)
- Radio Address for Halley, Station WLIB, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  November 1
- Lecture to Training Institute (Box 41, Folder 42a)
- Lecture to Training Institute (Box 41, Folder 42b)
- Lecture to Training Institute (Box 41, Folder 42c)
- 10th Anniversary Liberal Party dinner, Hotel Commodore (Box 41, Folder 43)
- Tex and Jinx show, Station WNBC, 1:00-2:00p.m. (2 sides), 1954 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  October 13
- Labor Day Parade, 1961 (Box 41a, Folder 1)
- Henoch Mendelsund; Local 117 meeting, 1960 (Box 41a, Folder 2)
  March 2
- Metropolitan report; Executive Vice President Fred Siems. WNBC Radio 66, 1979 (Box 41a, Folder 3)
  August 30
- Joint Board Insallation meeting; Henoch Mendelsund, New General Manager, 1959 (Box 41a, Folder 4)
  September 30
- Unity House (Box 41a, Folder 5)
- Adlai Stevenson; Labor-Liberal Party Rally Manhattan Center, NYC, 1954 (Box 41a, Folder 6)
  October 29
- Jinx Diary, WNBT, Channel 4, 2:30-3:00p.m. (1 side), 1954 (Box 41a, Folder 45)
- Tex and Jinx show; Station WNBC, 11:20p.m.-12:30a.m. (2 sides), 1954 (Box 41a, Folder 46)
- David Dubinsky address to the 1955 Training Institute Class (Box 41a, Folder 46b)
  May 10
- Manhattan Center Labor-Liberal Party Rally, 1954 (Box 41a, Folder 47)
- David Dubinksy staff conference re: office workers, 1955 (Box 41a, Folder 48)
  January 3
- David Dubinsky address to the 1955 Training Institute Class (Box 41a, Folder 49a)
- International House, Haifa, Israel; Merom (in Hebrew); David Dubinsky (in Yiddish), 1955 (Box 41a, Folder 50a)
  June 5
- International House, Haifa, Israel (Yiddish translation of Merom), 1955 (Box 41a, Folder 50b)
- Bailinson Hospital Dedication, 1955 (Box 41a, Folder 51)
  June 19; Tel Aviv; David Dubinsky, Sprinzak; Broadcast Station, WLIB
- David Dubinksy report on trip, Hotel Astor (2 sides), 1955 (Box 41a, Folder 52a)
  June 29
- Meeting of Puerto Rican Garment Workers re: Minimum Wage, 1955 (Box 41a, Folder 53)
  July 14
- Cloakmaker Joint Board (Box 42, Folder 7)
- #26 W.C. Home Dedication (Box 42, Folder 8)
- #27 Graduation 2nd Class (Box 42, Folder 9)
- #28 Cloak Joint Board (Box 42, Folder 10)
- [unlabeled] (Box 42, Folder 11)
- [unlabeled] (Box 42, Folder 12)
- [unlabeled] (Box 42, Folder 13)
- [unlabeled] (Box 42, Folder 14)
- [unlabeled] (Box 42, Folder 15)
- [unlabeled] (Box 42, Folder 16)
- [unlabeled] (Box 42, Folder 17)
- [unlabeled] (Box 42, Folder 18)
- WFDR C551 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Opening Session; ILGWU convention; Civic Opera House, Chicago, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Julius Hochman Birthday, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  January 12
- 1958 Strike; Dress Northeast Department meeting (Box 42, Folder 22)
  David Dubinsky; Julius Hochman
- Juliuis Hochman 60th birhtday, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  David Dubinsky; Julius Hochman; January 12
- ILGWU 1948 Campaign Committee presents "Truman, Barkley and Labor" (Box 42, Folder 24)
- #661 ILGWU Labor Day, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  August 21
- Interview with Charles S. Zimmerman at YIVO, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  November 13
- Untitled (Box 42, Folder 27)
- Interview with Charles S. Zimmerman at YIVO, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  November 20
- Interview with Charles S. Zimmerman at YIVO, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  December 11
- Interview with Paulin Newman at YIVO, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  January 26
- Interview with Pauline Newman at YIVO, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  February 2
- David Dubinsky;National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board Meeting, 1959 (Box 42a, Folder 32)
  Miami Beach, Florida; February 2
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board Meeting; Miami Beach, Florida, 1959 (Box 42a, Folder 33)
  Feb. 24; David Dubinsky
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board Meeting; Miami Beach, Florida, 1959 (Box 42a, Folder 34)
  Feb. 4; David Dubinsky
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board Meeting, 1959 (Box 42a, Folder 35)
  Feb. 2; Cong. Wright Patman
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board Meeting, 1959 (Box 42a, Folder 36)
  Feb. 2; Con. Wright Patman
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board Meeting, 1959 (Box 42a, Folder 37)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board Meeting, 1959 (Box 42a, Folder 38)
- Sam Zackman, A.M-P.M. (2 sides), 1957 (Box 42a, Folder 39)
  July 31
- Sam Berger, P.M. (1 side), 1957 (Box 42a, Folder 40)
- Lester Washburn, A.M.(2 sides), 1957 (Box 42a, Folder 41)
  Aug. 1
- Side 1: Lester Washburn (continued), Topazio; Side 2: Topazio (continued), Abe Goldber, Gassner, p.m., 1957 (Box 42a, Folder 42)
- 8/1/57 P.M. continued to 47, Gassner (continued), 8/2/57 A.M. (2 sides), 1957 (Box 42a, Folder 43)
- 8/2/57 P.M. continued at #205, 8/6/57, O.M. Tuvim, 1957 (Box 42a, Folder 44)
- 8/8/57 P.M. -47: Dio re Washburns testimonial, 8/12/57: from 65 to end, Doris, 1957 (Box 42a, Folder 45)
- 8/12/57: P.M.; from #330, 8/13/57 A.M. Doris, 1957 (Box 42a, Folder 46)
- Hoffa, 1957 (Box 42a, Folder 47)
  Aug. 20
- Hoffa, A.M., 1957 (Box 42a, Folder 48)
  Aug. 21
- Hoffa, P.M. 1 and 2, 2nd side #338 re Dio, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Side 1: 8/21/57: Hoffa P.M.; Side 2: A.M. 8/22/57, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Sides 1 and 2: Hoffa A.M. and P.M., 1957 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  Aug. 22
- Sides 1 and 2: Hoffa A.M., 1957 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  Aug. 23
- M. Fleishman; CIO 13th convention, evening session, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  Nov. 5
- CIO Convention, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  Nov. 5; Murray, Part II
- Interview with CIO delegates, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  Joe Michaels; 15 IPS?
- Point of information. Opening and Closing sound effect, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  March 9
- Public hearing, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  July 19; 7.5 IPS
- Public hearing, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  July 19; Tyler; Collins; 7.5 IPS
- Public hearing, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Afternoon: Credential Committee, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  May 12; Chairman Falikman, Secretary Alfred King, Rules Committee, Chairman Bialis, Secretary Douglas Levin
- Afternoon: Committee on Special Labor Legislation, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  May 13
- Afternoon: Introduction to Roy Williams, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  May 17
- Afternoon: Revision of Constitution (continued), convention, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  May 19
- Afternoon: Dubinsky election, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  May 20; Stulberg cast [?] vote, Dubinksy accept, Stulberg election, Shoenwald [?], Ed Kramer, Chaikin, Harold Schwartz
- Golden Door Award Dinner to David Dubinsky (tape recording #1) (Box 43, Folder 17a)
  Welcome by Mr. Biddle, Mrs. Farkas, Mr. Biddle, Mr Heckscher, Introduction to reading of telegrams: Mayor Wagner, Mr. Richard F. Walsh, Mr. Samuels
- Golden Door Award Dinner to David Dubinsky (tape recording #2) (Box 43a, Folder 17b)
- Golden Door Award Dinner to David Dubinsky (tape recording #4) (Box 43a, Folder 17c)
  Mr. Dubinsksy's speech
- Golden Door Award Dinner to David Dubinsky (tape recording #3) (Box 43a, Folder 17d)
- David Dubinsky retirement, 1966 (Box 43a, Folder 18)
  March; General Executive Board
- Last day (Box 43a, Folder 19)
  reel on both sides
- David Dubinsky report (reel 3), 1966 (Box 43a, Folder 20)
- Dinner in honor of Ambassador Eban of Israel, 1959 (Box 43a, Folder 21)
  April 20; Hotel Biltmore, New York City
- [Tape presented to David Dubinsky], 1958 (Box 43a, Folder 22)
  ncludes notes on box and letter from the General Federation of Jewish Labour in Israel
- David Dubinsky: Man of Labor (Eternal Light Program), 1958 (Box 43a, Folder 23)
- David Dubinsky speech, 1958 (Box 43a, Folder 24)
  April 15; Jewish Community Center, Scranton, Pennsylvania
- David Dubinsky, National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, 1960 (Box 43a, Folder 25)
  Feb. 3; Barcelona Hotel, Miami Beach, Florida; 7.5 IPS
- Remarks by David Dubinksy following Mr. Horns address, 1961 (Box 43a, Folder 26)
  May 9; Hotel Shelbourne, Atlantic City, New Jersey (copy); 7.5 IPS
- Remarks by David Dubinksy following Mr. Horns address (Box 43a, Folder 27)
  May 9; Hotel Shelbourne, Atlantic City, New Jersey
- Remarks by David Dubinksy following Mr. Horns address, 1961 (Box 43a, Folder 28)
  May 9; Hotel Shelbourne, Atlantic City, New Jersey (copy)
- 25th Anniversary Dinner; Shamokin Local 185, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  Sept. 17; Pennsylvania; Address by Sol C. Chaikin and Rosato; part 2;t aken from Northeast Department records, 103/50
- Cloak Joint Board Installation, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  Apr.2; David Dubinsky; Hotel Astor
- Political campaign, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  Nov. 2;' Carl Sandberg; ILGWU; Single trak, 7.5 IPS
- Mrs. Eleanor Roosevelt, unedited, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  Oct. 7; 7.5 IPS
- 1910 Strike celebration, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  Tape from radio
- 1910 Strike celebration, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  Chorus; Opening speeches; Mendelsund; Meany; Dubinsky (part)
- 1910 Strike Celebration, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  Chorus; Mendelsund; introduction to Dubinsky, Lehman; Tape used on radio
- 1910 Strike Celebration; Carnegie Hall, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  Sept. 17; Introduction to program; Chorus; Henoch Mendelsun and Introduction of H. Lehman, H. Lehman, H. Mendelsund introduction to Meany, Meany speech, Dubinksy speech; dual track tape, play both sides
- 50th Anniversary Celebration1910 Strike, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  Sept. 17; Carnegie Hall. The Songs Our People Sing: A Dramatic Episode; Written by Harry Gersh, directed by Herbert Machiz with Morris Carnovsky, Helen Menken, Jay Barney, Leo Lucker; Songs by Masha Benya
- Meeting of Joint Executive Boards (re negotiations), 1961 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  April 24; Hotel New Yorker, Chairman Ben Kaplan, Speakers H. Mendelsund, David Dubinsky, E. Howard Molisani
- Lecture to Training Institute Day Class, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  March 3; Sol "Chick" Chaikin; /75 IPS, taken from Northeast Department material 10/3/50?
- Reading Institute, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  Aug. 4; Recorded at Garden Room of Crystal Restaurant; 3/75 IPS, taken from Northeast Department material 10/3/50?
- Joint Installation Dinner, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  March 21; Hotel Astor, Chairman Mendelsund, Speakers J. Hochman, Antonini, Zimmerman, Stulberg
- Joint Installation meeting (Box 44, Folder 14)
  Hotel Astor, Local managers (all): Henoch Mendelsund, M.M. Kolker, David Dubinsky (side 2)
- Shop Chairman Meeting, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  Aug. 21; Hotel New Yorker. Chairman Molisani, Minn Matheson, J. Denaro, David Dubinsky, and Nat Windman
- U of M Roundtable, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  March 13; Miami Beach, Florida, Henoch Mendelsund, Dr. Vatican; Radio program, 7.5 IPS, full track
- Joint Board installation, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  March 20; Hotel Commodore, H. Molisani, Charles Zimmerman, Luigi Antonini, Henoch Mendelsund; side 2: H. Molisani and David Dubinsky
- Joint Board installation, 1965 (Box 44a, Folder 18)
  March 20; Hotel Commodore. W. Wirtz, Secretary of Labor
- Altmeyer luncheon, 1965 (Box 44a, Folder 19)
  Jan. 27; Astor Hotel. Side 1: Henoch Mendelsund, Monroe Goldwater, David Dubinsky; Side 2: Henoch Mendelsund, Joseph Dubow, Arthur Altemeyer
- Golden Jubilee, Philharmonic, 1966 (Box 44a, Folder 20a)
  Feb. 27; L[ocal?] 48, musical concert
- Golden Jubilee, Philharmonic, 1966 (Box 44a, Folder 20b)
  Feb. 27; L[ocal?] 48, musical concert (continued)
- Golden Jubilee, Philharmonic, 1966 (Box 44a, Folder 20c)
  Feb. 27; L[ocal?] 48, speech, tape
- Four Freedoms Award Luncheon, 1972 (Box 44a, Folder 21)
  Dec. 2; Hotel Commodore; Side 1: H.E. Egidio Ortona, Ambassadore of the Republic of Italy; Side 2: Murray Finley, Molisani introduction; response and address by Louis Stulberg; 7.5 IPS
- Report on Freedom, 1967 (Box 44a, Folder 22)
  Feb. 14; WEVD
- Fashion Institute, 1957 (Box 44a, Folder 23)
  Oct. 8
- Naglers speech re Meyer London (Box 44a, Folder 24)
  Side 1
- Nagler greets joint board, 1958 (Box 44a, Folder 25)
  Dec. 17
- A Word about YIVO at the 40th anniversary conference of YIVO, 1966 (Box 44a, Folder 26)
  May 1; Henoch Mendelsund; Commodore Hotel, New York City
- Dedication of Hazleton headquarters, 1960 (Box 44a, Folder 27)
  Aug. 22; Sol Chaikin; Taken from Northeast Department material, 10/3/50
- Unidentified (Box 44a, Folder 28)
  Taken from Northeast Department material, 10/3/50
- Forward Victor Reisel interview, 1966 (Box 44a, Folder 29)
  Nov. 15; WEVD Radio (AM and FM) New York, 8:00-8:30P.M., Louis Stulberg, "Labor and Elections"; Side 1, I mil polyester, 3.74 IPS
- Unidentified (Box 44a, Folder 30)
- No Negro Need Apply, NBC-TV, 1962 (Box 44a, Folder 31)
  Nov. 4; 7.5 IPS
- Demonstration [1 of 4 tapes; two tapes have songs] (Box 44a, Folder 32)
  Taken from Northeast Department material
- Demonstration [2 of 4 tapes; two tapes have songs] (Box 44a, Folder 33)
- Demonstration [3 of 4 tapes; two tapes have songs] (Box 44a, Folder 34)
- Demonstration [4 of 4 tapes; two tapes have songs] (Box 44a, Folder 35)
- Address, Mr. John E. Horn and remarks, 1961 (Box 44a, Folder 36)
  May 9; Hotel Shelburne, Atlantic City, New Jersey (copy); 7.5 IPS, full track, 11:52
- Address, Mr. John E. Horn and remarks, 1961 (Box 44a, Folder 37)
  May 9; Hotel Shelburne, Atlantic City, New Jersey; 7.5 IPS, full track, 11:52 A.M.
- Address, Mr. John E. Horn and remarks, 1961 (Box 44a, Folder 38)
- Address, Secretary of Labor Arthur Goldberg, 1961 (Box 44a, Folder 39)
  May 8; Hotel Shelburne, Atlantic City, New Jersey (copy); 7.5 IPS, 10:00 A.M.
- Address, Secretary of Labor Arthur Goldberg, 1961 (Box 44a, Folder 40)
  May 8; Hotel Shelburne, Atlantic City, New Jersey; 7.5 IPS, 10:00 A.M.
- Address, Secretary of Labor Arthur Goldberg, 1961 (Box 44a, Folder 41)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, 1960 (Box 44a, Folder 42)
  Feb. 1; Senator John Sparkman; Barcelona Hotel, Miami Beach, Florida; Master, 7.5 IPS
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, 1960 (Box 44a, Folder 43)
  Feb. 1; Senator John Sparkman; Barcelona Hotel, Miami Beach, Florida; 7.5 IPS
- Speeches of Longhena [Lanphena?], 1952 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  March; Parri, Canini, Pastore (Local 89); Audiodiscs, Audio Devices, Inc., NYC
- Civil rights speeches, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  Oct.20; Stevenson, Humphrey, Douglas, Kennedy
- ILGWU Speakers, Local 48, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  Feb. 27; Philharmonic Hall
- United Auto Workers (UAW) Convention, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 4a-b)
  April 17; Speech by David Dubinsky, introduced by Walter Reuther [1 reel of 2]; 7.5 IPS
- A.A. Berle, ILGWU, Listwords, ILGWU 106 Campaign Committee, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  Oct. 6
- ILGWU, WWDC, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  Oct. 18; 15 IPS
- Tex and Jinx Radio, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  Oct. 12; WNBC, 11:20 P.M. 12:00 A.M.
- Tex and Jinx Radio, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  Oct. 13; WNBC, 1:00 2:00 P.M.
- Unidentified (Box 45, Folder 9)
- ILGWU, Mrs. Franklin D. Roosevelt, Senator Wayne Moore, Senator Lehan, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  Oct. 14; 15 and 7.5 IPS
- Mrs Franklin D. Roosevelt, ILGWU, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  Oct. 7; !: Spots; II: ILGWU Series (Humphrey); III: Civil Rights Series; 15 IPS
- Sections of Local 62 Fire Warden meeting, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  Sept. 4
- Local 62, Fire Warden conference, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- The Man Who Would Not Bargain (Box 46, Folder 3)
  written and directed by Pat Daniels, narrated by Joseph Wiseman, re David Dubinsky; 7.5 IPS, full track mono
- The Garment Game, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  june 24; 7.5 IPS, dual track tape
- General Executive Board Health and Welfare Fund Committee, Retirement, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  Feb. 14
- ILGWU, George M. Leader and David Dubinsky (from) Wilkes Gymnasium, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 6a)
  Nov. 16
- Wyoming Valley District, 20th Anniversary Dinner, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 6b)
  Nov. 16; President Dubinsky and Government Leader
- Housing dedication of Penn Station South, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 7a)
  May 19; [reel 1 of 2]
- Housing dedication of Penn Station South, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 7b)
  May 19; [reel 2 of 2]
- David DubinskyLouis Stulberg at Cutters Local 10, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  March 28
- Brandeis Dinner, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  March 6
- Louis Stulberg, Jewish Labor Committee, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  Nov. 23; Cut#2
- Italian-American Labor Council 35th Anniversary (Box 46, Folder 11)
  Chairman E. Howard Molisani into [intr?] to President Louis Stulberg; 7.5 IPS
- From Precinct to President Some Reflections by Harry S. Truman, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 12a)
  Feb.2 ;10:00 11:00 P.M. [reel 1 of 2]; 7.5 IPS
- From Precinct to President Some Reflections by Harry S. Truman, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 12b)
  Feb. 6; 10:00 11:00 P.M. [reel 1 of 2]; 7.5 IPS
- This reel contains the sighn [sic?] on and opening Symphany [sic] Theme (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Interview with Dora Maizler re Triangle Fire, 1957 (Box 263, Folder 1)
  April 12; Redwood City, California; 3.75 IPS; 2nd copy on audiocassette
- Interview with Mr. Max Hochfield re Triangle Fire, 1957 (Box 264, Folder 1)
  Jan. 20; 3.75 IPS; 2nd copy on audiocassette
- Triangle Factory Fire Memorial, 1961 (Box 46a, Folder 16)
  March 25; as broadcast over WNYC; 7.5 IPS
- Tex and Jinx (Box 46a, Folder 17)
  12:00 12:30 A.M.; 7.5 IPS?
- Tex and Jinx Jury, 1961 (Box 46a, Folder 18)
  March 25; Leon Stein; 7.5 IPS, half track tape
- As We See It (Box 46a, Folder 19)
  7.5 IPS, full track; subject: the Triangle Fire, participants: Frances Perkins, Leon Stein, reporter: Harry W. Flannery
- Henoch Mendelsund (Box 46a, Folder 20)
- Kenrose Strike Rally, 1960 (Box 46a, Folder 21)
  June 21; Dubinsky, speaker; Roanoke, Virginia; 3.75 IPS, 1 side only
- Lyndon B. Johnson [speaking to?] ILG, 1967 (Box 46a, Folder 22)
  Nov. 9
- Dr. Lawrence Bethel, President Fashion Institute of Technology, 1960 (Box 46a, Folder 23)
  Feb. 3
- [copy of #23?] (Box 46a, Folder 24)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, 1960 (Box 46a, Folder 25)
  Feb. 3; David Dubinsky; Barcelona Hotel, Miami Beach, Florida; 7.5 IPS
- Public Service Forum, Are Unions Necessary, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  Aug. 6; John Snyder and Ralph Reuter
- Public Service Forum, Civil Rights 1962 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  Oct. 18; Jacob Shlitt, Education Director, Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Boar, interviewed by Dr. Ralph Reuter
- Public Service Forum, The Problems Facing the New Congress, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  Nov. 15; Representative Edward Boland (D-Massachusetts), interviewed by Dr. Ralph Reuter
- Public Service Forum, The Role of the University in Higher Education, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  May 3; O. Meredith Wilson, President of the University of Minnesota, interviewed by Ralph Reuter
- Public Service Forum, The Challenge of the World of Tomorrow, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  June 21; Walter Reuther, United Auto Workers, interviewed by Dr. Ralph Reuter
- Public Service Forum, Will the Far East Provoke a World War?, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  Jan. 31; Dr. David N. Rowe, Professor of political science at Yale University, interviewed by Ralph M. Reuter
- Public Service Forum, War or Peace, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  Feb. 7; Walter Reuther, United Auto Workers, interviewed by Dr. Ralph Reuter
- Public Service Forum, Can U.S. High Wages Compete?, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  Feb. 21; Bert Seldman, economist, AFL-CIO, interviewed by Dr. Ralph Reuter
- A 638 Tape #6 ILGWU, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Spanish Lesson #1-20 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- David Gingold, CYC (Box 47, Folder 11)
  March 26?
- Strike in Danville [part I], 1951 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  Aug. 7
- Strike in Danville [part II], 1951 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Gompers, Dubinsky (Box 47, Folder 14)
- A & B Reuther Press Conference, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- ILGWU The Legacy, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Public Service Forum, The Role of Unions in Our Society, 1962 (Box 47a, Folder 17)